you can now scrape any website for free
with AI using Firecrawl.
This is great for anyone who's building
an AI agent, an SEO tool, or just a data
extraction script.
It will basically turn your website
into this very clean, structured dataset,
which is very useful.
I've personally been using this to track
product launches and just launches
in general from different startups.
All my homies love Firecrawl.
It literally handles all the complexities
for you, and it's super fast.
Also, they have a student program
where they can give you 10K free credits
for any educational or personal project.
So if you have a student
email, that would be good.